https://canadian-passport-support.com/privacy-policy/

Top MenuHomeHow to Apply for Your Passport in 5 StepsAbout UsPrivacyContact UsPowered by IMMIgroupNavigation
Home
Home Canada Passport FAQCanadian Birth Certificate FAQCanadian Death Certificate FAQMarriage to a Foreigner FAQPR Card FAQTravel Related FAQRight of Citizenship FAQCanadian Visa FAQUK Vital Statistics Certificates FAQCanadian Pardon FAQReplacement Citizenship Card FAQFAST Card FAQGlobal Entry FAQNEXUS Card FAQTravel Document FAQWork Holiday Visa FAQ (IEC)US Waiver FAQBritish Passport FAQCanada Sponsorship FAQContact UsPrivacy PolicyDisclaimerAbout UsInternational Visas FAQHomeExpress Entry FAQElectronic Travel Authorization (eTA) FAQHow to Apply for Your Passport in 5 Steps
Return to Content
Canadian Passport Support Privacy PolicyCanadian Passport Support respects your privacy. As we develop our online presence, we will revise our Privacy Policy to reflect our practices and to meet any legislative or other requirements. The terms of this Privacy Policy form part of and should be read in conjunction with the Disclaimer which governs this Website. Collection of Personal InformationCanadian-Passport-Support is the sole owner of the information collected on Canadian-Passport-Support.com. Canadian-Passport-Support collects personally identifiable information from our users at only one point on our Website – signing up for our newsletter. Use and Disclosure of InformationWe will use personal information you provide to us for the purpose of providing you with the information you have requested. We do not share personally identifiable information with third parties. We will not sell, rent, trade, share, reveal or disclose any of your personal information, unless you have specifically requested that we do so; we deem it necessary to provide you with products you have requested; we are required to do so by a Court of competent jurisdiction or by a governmental order, decree, regulation or rule of any regulatory agency; we reasonably believe that use of disclosure is necessary to prevent or lessen a serious and imminent threat to an individual’s life, health or safety or a serious threat to public health or safety; or we have reason to suspect that unlawful activity has been, is being or may be engaged in and the use or disclosure of your personal information is a necessary part of our investigation of the matter or in reporting our concerns to relevant persons or authorities.We may provide aggregate information and statistics about Canadian-Passport-Support visitors, sales traffic patterns and related site information to third parties but these statistics will not include individual personal information. CookiesCookies are pieces of information that a website can transfer to an individual’s web browser on their computer hard drive for record keeping.Cookies can make using websites easier by storing information about your preferences on a particular website. The information remains on your computer after the Internet session finishes.Canadian-Passport-Support cookies to improve the functionality of its site and support all browsers. Canadian-Passport-Support uses cookies to assess the performance of the Website and to confirm your preferences.Most Internet browsers are pre-set to accept cookies. If you prefer not to receive cookies, you can adjust your Internet browser to refuse cookies or to warn you when cookies are being used. These cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information. Data SecurityCanadian-Passport-Support takes your privacy and the privacy of all its visitors very seriously. We have practices which include the secure storage of personal information and safeguards against the accidental release of personal information.If you have any concerns about your privacy and the use of the Website or any of Canadian-Passport-Support’s services, please contact our Legal Department at info@canadian-passport-support.com for further assistance. Links to Other SitesThis Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Canadian-Passport-Support. Please be aware that we, Canadian-Passport-Support, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Website. Changes to Privacy PolicyWe reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. Contact Us If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at info@canadian-passport-support.com.Sign Up For Newsletter*
All FAQs Canada Passport British Passport Express Entry Sponsor Your Spouse Marriage to a Foreigner Electronic Travel Authorization (eTA) Permanent Resident Card Right of Citizenship Replacement Citizenship Card Canadian Visa International Visas Related to Travel Canadian Pardon Fast Card Global Entry NEXUS Card Travel Document Work Holiday Visa US Waiver Canadian Birth Certificate Canadian Death Certificate UK Vital Statistics Certificates FAQApplications Birth, Death, Marriage Certificates
International Visas
Marriage to a Foreigner
Permanent Resident Card
Right of Citizenship
UK Certificates
Citizenship Card
FAST Card
NEXUS Card
Travel Document
Work Holiday Visa
US Waiver
British Passport
Canada SponsorshipFree Web Widgets & Mobile AppsImmigroup ForumGet your immigration, visa and travel document questions answered in the Immigroup forum.Find an Immigration Professional for CanadaSearch our directory of Immigration Lawyers, Registered Immigration Consultants and Quebec Notaires, some of whom have offices overseas.Embassies & Consulates DirectoryLocate the nearest Embassy or Consulate of any country in Canada.Canada/US Border Crossing DirectoryEvery US-Canada Border Crossing: Maps, Directions, Ratings, Tolls, Alternate Crossings, Photos, Videos.Travel Vaccine DirectoryGoing on a trip? Check this directory for vaccines needed for all parts of the world.ESL / Immigration Centre DirectoryFind the nearest ESL school or Immigration Help Centre in your neighbourhood.This site is powered byHomeAbout UsPrivacy PolicyDisclaimerContact UsPowered by IMMIgroup
